Simon!
Keri!
Daddy?
Dad!
Babe, is everything okay?
Sorry, I was just
looking for a record.
Well, come on.
We're not gonna see
everyone for a while.
Right, sorry.
By the way,
everyone thinks it's cute
we're matching.
Babe?
Yeah.
Just give me a sec.
He really agreed to
go along with this?
Yes.
He's excited.
Are you sure it's
what you want?
What do you mean?
You know I love Tim,
but he hasn't been
that Tim in a while.
Like, aren't you worried
about how long it's been since
the two of you have, like,
you know, why don't
you take the job
and find a country boy
who actually fucks you?
Hey.
Oh, sick.
I didn't know you
still did music.
Yeah, uh,
actually just finishing
up a new EP.
Sick.
You still on the same label?
Probably self releasing
this time.
But, hey, I heard you guys
got booked on
the whole Sound Off tour.
That's--that's awesome.
Dude, you gotta get back
on a label.
They just book you
on so much stuff.
That's so true.
Yeah, no, I should
just get back on a label.
He's still going
through a lot.
Honestly, it's another reason
why I think this move
will be good for both of us.
Okay.
This is so exciting.
Do you think he knows?
He has no idea.
You know, we need a
guitarist for the tour.
What?
For real?
I figured, you know, with the
move that you're written off.
Shit.
I mean, I could check-in
with Millie, but...
When you started dating
my sister,
I thought you might make
her cooler.
Instead, she's just
made you...
Hey, fuck you, man.
Nah, it's cool, it's just
when I die, I don't want
someone else's life
flashing before my eyes.
Alright, I'll do it. The tour.
Oh, that's dope.
Uh, there's a lot
of rehearsals.
I'll make it back.
It's not even that far.
And it's so fucking far.
Look, this isn't that
big of a deal.
It's just a couple hours away.
Says the prick
who can't drive.
Who needs to drive
in the city?
Obviously, we're gonna miss
you guys a lot.
This insane group is,
you know, it's
the family I got.
So...
but I--
I'm so proud of Millie.
You are the sweetest,
most giving person
I've ever met.
These kids don't even know
how lucky they are
to get someone who actually
cares about their education.
Aww.
So, um, yeah.
It's-- it's all bittersweet.
I'm a little scared, but,
uh, mainly excited
about the next step
in our lives together.
Woo!
Yeah.
That's it.
Okay.
Relax.
It's just a change of scenery.
Babe.
In front of the people
who mean the most to us,
I wanna ask you...
to spend the rest of your
life with me.
Are you joking?
Uh...
Oh.
Yes. Of course.
Yes.
I, I, I do.
I'm sorry.
I fucking suck.
Okay? I just, I didn't know
what was happening,
and I froze.
You still want this, right?
It's a little late now, right?
Yeah, it fucking is.
But still, if we don't
split now,
it'll only be harder later.
Wait, like "split" split?
Is that what you want?
No, of course not.
I don't know.
You've been so distant
since...
and that's okay.
Of course.
It's just...
you've never made
me feel unsure before.
Unsure of what?
If we love each other
or if we're just
used to each other.
Hey, hey, I'm sorry.
Okay?
Sorry.
I think I drank too much.
It's okay.
Hey, hey, I love you.
I love you too.
Everyone knows you need me
more than I need you.
We laugh about it.
What?
Resenting me doesn't make
you less of a failure.
Why are you saying this?
Can you ask them to leave?
Who?
I can't sleep with
them staring at us.
Good morning.
You clearly don't miss
the sound of traffic.
How long you been up?
Not long.
Figured one of these
had to have
the coffee machine inside.
Do you think I resent you?
Well, now.
Sorry.
Still half asleep.
Because you're looking
at your dream girl.
That must be it.
Since you're out here,
can you bring
something inside?
Sure, yeah.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Careful.
This is worrying.
Your dad's?
Maybe I could use it
to fix the back porch.
Never let me use that.
Hey, babe,
do you smell that?
I'm peeing.
You really don't
smell anything?
What's going on?
Babe?
Oh, Jesus.
Ugh!
Babe, what are you doing?
I found it.
What?
Oh, sh--
Oh god.
How'd you know
to look for that?
Excuse me.
Hi.
Did you bring that from
home or take it from my tin?
Oh, sorry.
I thought that they were
just for the staff,
but I don't have a...
Sugar?
No.
Thank you.
How much trouble am I in?
Oh, God.
Don't mind Carol.
She's possessive of
dry old bags
on account of her being one.
It's Ms. Wilson, right?
Millie.
I'm Jamie, welcome.
Thank you.
I gotta say,
I was so happy
you took this placement.
Your resume really
caught my eye.
You saw that?
Yeah, well, I was part
of the hiring committee.
Wanna sit?
Mhmm.
Uh, yeah, I was just thrilled
that someone of your caliber
was interested in our
tiny neck of the woods.
Oh, are you kidding?
I'm excited.
My old school was huge.
Students and staff all
lost in the shuffle.
Here, I'm hoping to actually
help these
kids as individuals.
Oh, passion.
Almost forgot what
that was like.
And you settling in okay?
You and your husband
or sorry,
your wife, or...
Me and my,
God...
boyfriend sounds so immature.
Partner?
My Tim?
My-- me and my
boy partner, Tim.
Have you, uh,
have you explored much?
Partners?
Oh, God, no, no.
No, the area.
Have you-- have you like,
where did you move to?
We, uh, we're down at the
end of Pitt Road.
This is so predictably
small town
to say this, but I
think we're neighbors.
Yeah, I'm in the yellow house
on the corner.
Oh, you're kidding.
Yeah, it's a great spot.
I mean, it's a
little ways from town,
but the woods and the
trails are amazing.
Well, uh...
let me know if, uh,
you ever need someone
to show you around,
you and
your boy partner.
- Sure.
- Have a good day.
Bye.
- How's it going?
- Hey.
Oh, do we have Internet?
Uh, guys coming next week.
Hey, you obviously
can't drive me back
for this gig on
Thursday, right?
I could take you
to the train station.
Okay, yeah, thanks.
Come to bed with me.
I have to learn
these parts.
Okay.
What about tomorrow?
Do you maybe wanna
do that hike
you were
telling me about?
Yeah.
That'd be great.
Great.
Okay.
Love you.
Is this it?
I don't know.
This feels short.
Did we miss something?
Hey, what about that?
Seems pretty overgrown.
Hon, I don't wanna
be the dumb city folk
who went against
nature and lost.
It's marked, we're good.
Babe.
We can always turn back.
It's just,
it's so nice out.
Okay, wait.
I think it's this way.
No, honey, I think
it was back there.
Are you sure?
No.
Are you?
Okay.
That way is North.
What do we do with that?
I don't know.
I thought it would be helpful.
Okay.
What if we just keep going
sort of, South East-ish?
Can't we just think
for a second.
Wait, no, no, babe,
this looks right, come on.
Babe!
Oh my God!
- Babe!
- Honey!
- Oh my God!
Oh my God, here!
Are you okay?
I think so.
Oh my God.
My phone.
Shit.
Can you call it?
I don't have a signal.
Fuck.
My demos were on there.
I'm fine, by the way.
- Hey, sorry, you okay?
- Yeah, it's okay.
You sure?
I'm okay.
What is this place?
Do you feel that?
It feels...
Crowded.
We gotta get out of here.
Back into the storm?
What is all this?
We can build a fire.
Wait it out.
Why do you have a lighter?
Does that really
matter right now?
How big is this place?
Let me check.
Hello?
Well?
Pretty big.
Honey.
Hmm?
What are you doing?
Remember when we used to
watch Man versus Wild?
Yeah.
You fucking don't.
Okay.
Thank you.
I am so thirsty.
Yeah, me too.
Is that all we have?
Yeah.
You think that's drinkable?
I'm not drinking it.
Alright, finish this.
What about you?
I found another bottle.
Okay.
What's that?
The other bottle.
Babe.
I wouldn't.
Man versus wild, babe.
No, it's fine, here.
So...
about that lighter.
When?
Just before the move.
You?
Same.
When we're out of here,
we'll both stop again.
Definitely.
For now, it's a nice
distraction
from all the rats that
must be down here.
I keep thinking about that
thing you found the other day.
Me too.
Hey.
What happened there?
When I was a kid,
my dad comes home
one day and tells me
to clean my room because he
says there's a smell,
so I clean it.
Next day, he comes home,
says it's still there,
so I clean it again.
Day after that,
he comes in, but
this time he's freaking out,
he's like...
what is that goddamn smell?
And he just starts tearing
my room apart,
but he can't find anything.
And at this point,
I'm scared because...
there is no smell.
You know?
I don't know why he's
getting so worked up.
Anyway, I um...
come home from school
the next day,
I go in my room,
and he's standing there
with this,
this wicked grin because
he found it.
It was a dead rat.
It had been nesting
above the warm light.
And every time I used that
light, I was cooking it.
But it was so gradual that,
I couldn't even tell that
I was breathing in this
this rotting carcass
every night.
Can't believe I haven't
heard that story before.
I had forgotten all about it
until the night
I found them.
And there's this detail
that I never told you,
never told anyone
about the smell.
But it was worse than that.
It was like a-- like a taste.
Like the air was thick,
and it just got worse
the closer I got to
their bedroom.
Then I opened the door.
She was smiling at me.
She had woke to find her
other half was gone
and her brain just snapped.
She couldn't process it.
Still going to bed each night
next to that
face and that horrible smell.
I was standing there
choking on the taste of him
and she didn't even notice.
It's like me with the rat,
just breathing him in
like fresh air.
Sorry.
It's like a window opened
between our house
and that night.
What?
Only you could sleep-in
in a wet cave.
What time is it?
Oh, shit.
That sucks.
Let's just get home.
But my demos were on there.
I hate you.
No you don't.
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
What is that?
Wait, stop, stop, stop.
What the fuck?
What is it?
Mildew or something.
Ow, ow, that hurts.
I know,
what do you want to do
a fucking three legged race?
Sorry.
Slow, slow.
Ew.
Oh my god.
Fuck, fuck.
You were pretty
impressive in there.
Remember when I found North?
We should head into town.
There's no food in the house.
There used to be rice.
Well, we haven't
exactly budgeted
for two new phones.
But first...
What?
Just two minutes.
- Babe.
- Come on.
I just spent the night
in a cave.
- Please, please.
- Fine.
Alright, but you do me next.
Mhmm.
Babe, come on.
Babe?
Mmmm.
Ow, Tim?
Tim, Tim!
- What?
- What the fuck?
I-- I'm sorry.
Ugh, you trying to be funny?
That really hurt.
Honey, you don't look so good.
I'm-- I'm just really tired.
I'm gonna head into town.
I can come.
No, you just relax.
Maybe take a shower, yeah?
Says here you've dealt with
anxiety, panic attacks.
Is it possible this
is one of those?
No.
I don't think so.
How old are you?
We're actually the same age.
I see there's a history of
mental illness in the family.
Your mother suffered from--
No, it's nothing like that.
This is different.
I think it's worth discussing
what happened to her.
I've had this
conversation before.
I'm not her.
You have someone to talk to?
Family, a therapist, friends?
Yeah, I got friends
back in the city.
So locally,
it's just your wife?
Partner, yeah,
it's just her.
You had this dangerous
experience
when you're left alone
in an unfamiliar place,
no one to help if something
were to go wrong,
anxiety can fixate on a
thought like that,
and spiral into
a physical panic response.
This is technically
a muscle relaxant,
meaning it slows the central
nervous system down.
So even if your brain
starts panicking,
your body relaxes,
shutting down
the feedback loop.
- OK?
- Yeah.
You know,
you two were lucky.
There was that couple that
went missing out there.
What? When?
There's still posters up.
Biggest news this town's
seen for a while.
Bigger than local man
waters garden?
I'm serious.
There was a big search
and everything.
Valium?
It's called Diazepam now.
All ready for tomorrow?
Huh?
Honey, if you're not
feeling well,
maybe you should cancel.
Babe, if I cancel, I can
forget about the tour.
Hey, we didn't get
much data, yeah,
Maybe we don't use it
all, what are you...
Cruising for chicks online?
You know people went missing
around here recently?
Really?
Yeah.
Hey, do me a favor,
when I die, please
just nuke any and
all of my social media
from existence.
I don't wanna be
remembered for posting
nature is what home
feels like and
getting 23 likes.
They post this,
and that's it.
Cool.
Great life.
Okay.
So if you die tonight,
what's your final post?
We took the plunge.
Aw.
That is so fucking basic.
Why would you tag me in that?
Because all this
shit is basic, Tim.
Nobody cares.
It's just so, like,
my mom can see.
Plus, you love it.
Whatever.
That'd be a sad one
to end it on, though.
Yeah.
What wouldn't be?
BRB dying.
Literally,
who could that be?
- Hi.
- Hello.
I hope you don't mind.
I was in the
neighborhood and uh,
because I am
the neighborhood,
and I thought I would
officially welcome you
to said neighborhood.
Hey.
Hey, man.
Oh, babe.
This is Mr. McCabe.
Jamie, who I--
I've told you about him.
Right, oh yeah, hey.
You must be Tim,
the boy partner.
Nice to meet you.
I'm hoping you drink red.
Oh, Tim drinks anything.
Please come in.
Oh, no, no.
I don't wanna intrude.
Mr. McCabe,
I insist you intrude.
Alright.
Thanks.
Here, just to the left.
Mr. McCabe?
That's terrifying.
Well, it was more
just the rain.
It was pouring rain.
I mean, we were
totally disoriented.
Well, you know your
phone has a compass.
- Yeah.
Alright, let's not
get stuck on
who had which
cardinal directions.
Seriously, though,
have you
ever seen anything
like that out there?
I was getting, like,
cult vibes.
Cult vibes?
Honey, I don't know
about that.
What, were we not
in the same place?
It was a cave,
but there was like a
giant bell and church pews
in the walls.
It was fucking weird.
There was a--
a chapel out that way.
Okay.
But that collapsed
years ago.
It was just like in
the middle of nowhere?
Yeah, it was like this
new age-y
hippie dippy group.
Cult vibes.
What happened to them?
Mass suicide.
- No.
- Oh, God.
No.
I don't know.
They just kinda, I donno,
thinned out over time.
I think they moved on when
the weather
took the building.
Hard to recruit
new members when your
house of worship becomes
a subterranean lair.
I got it.
Thanks, honey.
Yeah.
Man, this food...
I might make a habit
of dropping by.
It's all Tim.
I can't cook to save my
life, and it's his fault.
Oh, it's my fault?
You're so good at this stuff.
I've never had to learn.
So if it weren't for me,
you'd know how to cook?
And if it weren't for me,
you wouldn't be the only
thirty something without
a driver's license.
I have a license.
He doesn't have
he has a learner's permit.
He can't actually drive a car.
It's a good deal, you know?
She gets a personal cook,
and I'm trapped here.
Trapped?
I can't even make it
to the train station
unless it fits your schedule.
Nobody's holding you
hostage, Tim.
No, hostages don't have
to cook their own food.
Well, it sounds to me like
you complete each other.
You think?
I mean, that's what I--
It's so weird.
Yeah.
Hey it was-- it was nice
to meet you, man.
Hey, you too.
Thanks again.
And, I'll see you tomorrow.
Yes, oh, yeah.
- Aw.
- Okay. Bye.
Bye.
He's friendly.
What?
Nah, I just,
I think he likes you.
No he doesn't.
Don't be weird.
Mhmm.
You seem pretty charmed
by him too.
Really?
Yeah.
You're right.
I might just follow him home.
- Yeah?
- And...
Tim...
Ow!
Did you just bite me?
- No.
- What...
is this,
you're all over me one minute,
and then the next--
- I, I didn't!
I just I...
Some-- something's off.
Ever since we've been
here, I just--
Stop with the excuses.
Excuses?
I'm not making this up, babe.
Tim, God, if you don't wanna
fuck me, Tim, just say it.
Mmm.
Babe.
You're on my hair.
Ow, honey.
Will you roll over,
you're on my hair.
Tim?
Ow!
What the fuck?
You ready?
I don't think you should go.
There's a surprise.
Are we really not gonna
talk about last night?
You're acting--
What? Crazy?
That's not what I was saying.
I was unconscious, okay,
I didn't know what I was doing.
If you're sick,
you should stay home.
Babe, come on,
I can't miss the train.
Please.
You're gonna be great.
You know, I'd drive you
the whole way if I could.
It's fine.
Listen, don't worry about
coming back here tonight.
You mad at me?
No, no, no.
I just mean stay out.
Enjoy the after party,
you know, sleep at Luke's
and actually
catch up with everyone.
No use coming back here
and feeling trapped.
Look, I didn't mean that.
Sure, but...
maybe some space
would be good.
Are you sure?
Escape. Be free.
Okay. Yeah.
You're right.
Thanks.
Oh, come on.
No, not now.
Cmon.
Alright.
Great work, team.
I'll see you after PE.
Anna, Mr. Richardson won't
like it if you're late.
Sorry, miss.
Are these your dogs?
Not anymore.
It sounds like
he's fucking lost it.
No.
I don't know.
I-- you know, honestly,
it's been hard.
Are you okay?
Like, do you need me
to come up there?
I-- fuck it.
I'm coming up there.
No, no, no.
I'm probably making it
sound worse than it is.
And anyway, my folks
are coming up
for lunch on Sunday, so,
yeah, he probably just needs
to see a familiar face.
Yeah, I just wanna make sure
you're okay.
I'm fine.
I like the quiet country life.
I'm the boring one.
You think you're boring
because,
what, you have an
actual proper job?
I love Tim,
but he is a 35 year old
white guy
who still thinks he's
gonna be a rock star.
That is fucking boring.
He's a good guy.
Is he?
Yes.
You know, I always think
about our first date.
I said my favorite band
was the Spice Girls.
I didn't realize he was, like,
this music snob guy.
And then he shows up
on our second date
with Spice on vinyl.
That is sweet.
But that was nearly
a decade ago.
What has he done lately?
I gotta go.
Why?
Millie, I need...
No, no, no.
What are you doing here?
I just,
I needed to see you.
Why aren't you on the train?
This is really
fucking weird, Tim.
It's like I'm thirsty
all over, but not now.
Not with you.
Tell me you want me.
I need you.
Don't stop. Please don't stop.
What are we doing?
Sorry, I just...
I had a feeling.
Don't apologize.
Let's just try it
at home next time.
And maybe don't wait so long.
Okay.
Now you gotta
get out of here.
What-- what are you doing?
What do you mean?
What, it's-- why are
you, like, tensing?
What?
I... babe it's...
Wait.
I'm stuck.
Ow.
It hurts.
I know, I know.
What the fuck.
Alright, just pull pull pull--
Hurry, hurry.
I can't, I can't
It's still stuck!
Tim, you have got to
get out of here, now!
I'm trying!
It's not fucking moving!
That hurts.
Tim...
Listen to me,
listen to me!
I'm sorry.
No, no.
Your feet.
Everything okay in there?
Just a sec.
Everything okay, Miss Wilson?
Sorry, I had to, uh...
Um...
Miss Wilson,
you know this is a...
bathroom for little boys.
Sorry, I um...
had to...
Go to class.
Everything's fine.
Next time, try to get
to the staff bathroom, yeah.
And you might want to, uh...
clean up.
Shit.
Babe.
Babe, come on, we're just
not gonna talk about this?
Do you understand
what you did today?
I could have been fired.
Or worse, like, like
arrested worse.
Wait, I didn't
make you do anything.
You don't fuck me
for months, then you
barge into my work with
that 'I need you' shit?
Yeah, you kinda did.
God, are you trying
to ruin this for me?
You know,
I have sat on the sidelines.
I have sacrificed so that
you've had space
to try to make your
impossible dreams come true.
Woah, I'm not gonna apologize
for taking some risks.
And I never can because
you use all the risk up.
I-- I moved here for you.
I left my whole life behind.
What life?
God, your music?
Then why aren't you
at your show?
Tim, if you think
I've trapped you,
why don't you fucking leave?
I can't.
I don't think I'm okay.
It's like my brain and
my body aren't talking.
You don't understand.
I guess I don't.
Wait, where are you going?
To clean up your mess.
Sound familiar?
Do you want me to come?
What do you want, Tim?
I can't make every
decision for you.
I'm not your fucking mother,
even if I'm starting
to feel like her.
What's that supposed to mean?
Like I'm living with
something that's dead.
- Millie.
- Hi.
Hey.
The yellow house
on the corner.
Yeah.
So today,
I just wanted
to apologize again.
I'm so embarrassed
about um,
Oh, that.
Oh, no.
Don't even mention it.
That's...
female
issues.
It's, please don't no.
Say no more, please.
Thanks.
Hey, what's wrong?
Sorry, um...
It's just been a
really stressful day.
Tim and I just
had a big fight.
Sorry.
This is not your problem.
Wanna come inside?
I don't wanna intrude.
Miss Wilson,
I insist you intrude.
I'll get you a
glass of water.
You sure I can't tempt
you with anything stiffer?
No.
Water's fine.
Thanks.
What's going on?
I don't know.
I keep thinking
this was a mistake.
Like,
since the move, Tim and I
haven't been on the same page.
Then maybe we haven't been on
the same page for a while
and we're just
too scared to admit it.
Do you, uh...
do you love each other?
I mean, yeah.
Of course.
Right? But,
I mean, I don't remember
life before Tim, so...
maybe we're just complacent.
Well, you know,
complacency can
sometimes simply be harmony.
Do you wanna hear something
I teach my 9th grade
history class?
Desperately.
Plato wrote that
the ancient Greeks
believed we were created
with four arms,
four legs, and a head
with two faces.
But, Zeus feared our power,
so he split us
into two separate parts,
dooming us to
spend our lives in
search of the other half.
If you think you've
found that,
don't be so quick
to let it go.
Well, if Plato says so.
Is it just you here?
Sorry.
That's none of my business.
Oh, no. Please, God.
I'm the one prying.
Uh, yeah, there were two
of us when we
first bought this place.
And we were probably
around the same age
as you guys,
probably had the same
issues, same fights.
And there was a brief time
where I actually
did walk away.
And it was liberating.
I had the freedom to
do whatever I wanted.
So what did you do?
Oh, nothing.
I was miserable.
Yeah.
I just didn't know
how to exist on my own.
I, I,
I even started to
miss the fights we had.
Yeah.
For better or worse,
I was me
because of him.
I bet you miss him.
You know,
I have a tape of my wedding
that I have been looking
for an excuse to, uh--
Uh, you know,
that sounds great,
but I should head back.
Thanks.
Next time.
Sorry.
Sorry, okay, I didn't know
where else to go.
Babe, you ready for bed?
Babe?
Are you asleep?
I'm sorry.
I wish I could be what either
of us wants me to be.
Oh, shit!
What? No. Come on.
What?
Fuck.
Mil?
Alright, fuck this!
Oh fuck!
Oh shit!
Baby, baby, wake up!
Wake up!
Millie, wake up!
Baby!
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
Maybe it was like a seizure.
A seizure?
Since when have you had
seizures or sleep walked?
It's probably stress,
and you're not helping.
Look, I think something
happened to me in the cave.
something that's
making me act insane.
And now it's like,
it's like it's in you too.
Alright, that missing couple,
those hikers,
they were on the same path
that took us to the cave.
What if whatever happened to
them is happening to us?
I feel fine.
Well, that's because
you're awake.
You're adrenalized.
Okay? I think it gets
worse at night.
It's like when
the mind gets tired,
the body can take over.
Listen to what you're saying.
Alright, remember that morning
our legs stuck together?
You said that was just mildew.
Since when do I know
anything about mildew?
I don't even know
what it fucking is.
After we had sex,
we couldn't separate.
Explain that.
It had been a while?
That always makes it
a little painful.
Babe.
Okay. Alright.
Put your hand up like this.
Try not to touch mine.
You'll feel it.
Babe, please.
This is ridiculous.
I'm going to bed.
Come on.
It's like we're magnetic,
babe, please.
I think you should sleep
in the spare room tonight.
I agree, we need to
keep our distance.
Babe, wait.
I know why you stopped.
Because the moment
you got there,
I wanted you to stop.
I felt it.
That's not...
it's...
that doesn't make any sense.
Then how come I know
exactly what you're feeling?
The pull, the thirst
in your bones, babe,
something inside us has
imprinted on each other.
We're sick, okay?
I can't explain it,
but it's that place.
It has to be.
- Tim.
- We need answers.
I'm gonna go back.
Go back?
Yeah, as soon as
there's light, I'll go.
You know my parents are
coming for lunch Sunday?
Yeah, why?
I don't think you
should be here.
What does that mean?
It means,
I don't want you...
I don't want you.
I love you.
Okay.
What the fuck...
Oh, God!
Why is this happening?
Ahh, Millie!
Fight it!
Baby, you gotta fight it!
Ah!
I just want to die!
Baby, look at me.
Stay with me.
We can do this.
Okay, do what?
The drugs,
the pills... the drawer.
What?
Muscle-
relaxant!
Valium, Valium!
It's called diazepam now.
Fucking child-lock!
Hold it out!
How many?
Just take them, just...
It'll kick in quicker
if we snort them!
Just put your feet
against mine...
and then push away!
I can't do it.
Yes, you can.
You're so fucking strong.
You can do this.
Push, baby.
We only need to last
a couple minutes.
Push!
We got this!
I can do it.
We got this.
Just keep pushing.
Keep pushing!
Just keep pushing!
Just keep...
Just keep pushing...
Babe?
I was hoping I'd have more
time before you woke up.
It's gonna be okay.
What's going on?
Sorry, we don't have time for
you to "hem" and "haw"
about this.
About what?
Woah babe, this is a
weird time for a joke.
It's not getting worse,
so the drugs must still
be in our system, right?
Wait.
Wait, wait.
Babe, babe,
I wasn't even sure
that was the right tool
to fix the fucking porch.
Listen, when the pills
wear off,
it's gonna start again.
No, babe, babe, babe.
Imagine what you're about
to do actually happening,
and tell me that's not gonna
make things way worse.
Whiskey for the pain...
and as soon as
we're separated,
I'll sprint for
the first aid kit.
We have bandages,
disinfectant,
everything we need!
Ah, you're right handed.
Oh, God.
Actually, maybe that's
enough of that.
What, why?
I think I can
feel your whiskey.
You're right
handed and drunk.
Remember when you said you
weren't holding me hostage?
Do you think
I wanna do this?
No. So don't.
We are out of time.
We need to do this
while the drugs
are still in our system,
then we can get help.
I'm sorry.
We have to.
If we don't split now,
it'll be much harder later.
There's gotta be another way.
Do it.
Ahh!
- Sorry.
- Ahh!
Sorry.
Okay.
Careful, Careful!
Alright, I'm doing it.
Then do it!
I'm doing it.
Just do it.
Then do it!
By the way, I'm sorry I
didn't believe you before.
You were right, obviously.
Babe, just go!
I'm gonna go.
Stop, a doctor isn't gonna
be able to fix this!
Get in the trunk.
We need to keep as much
distance as possible.
- No
- Honey, the pills are
gonna wear off.
I know, but more pills
is just a band aid.
We need answers.
Tim, I just sawed
through our fucking arms.
We are going to the hospital.
Okay.
Oh wait... Shit.
What?
What's going on?
My keys.
I think I left them
at Jamie's.
Why-- why would you do that?
I didn't do it on purpose.
- Sorry.
- Come on.
You coming?
I'll wait.
Like you said, distance.
Tim, don't do anything stupid.
Jamie?
I'm so sorry,
it's-- it's me.
I'm just...
we need help.
It's,
it's serious...
Shit.
Jamie?
Hello?
What the fuck?
The happiest day of our life.
I'll give these back,
don't worry.
What is this?
The beginning of
something wonderful.
the fuck?
Help me!
Stay away from me.
We were scared at first too.
Everybody is,
but this is a great gift.
Such lucky few are we
who become whole.
No, I don't want this.
The connection is deeper than
anything you could
ever imagine.
No more walls.
Share fears and memories.
This is the hardest part.
You just have to push through.
Please.
What awaits is the ultimate
intimacy in divine flesh.
Stop it.
It's already happening.
You wouldn't like
the alternative.
Help me!
Millie!
Rejoice in the intimacy
that awaits.
No dissonance, only warmth.
I'm sorry, but it's best
to be open for each other.
It will hurry things along.
Ah!
The God's jealousy has robbed
you of your perfect form.
Yet divine happiness
is flowing through us.
You will be so warm.
Help me.
Come back.
Ahh!
Don't come any closer.
I know, I know!
This thing,
it's happened before.
We're not the first.
I know.
You went there.
Oh shit!
I saw something down there.
I think I know how to stop it.
What are you doing?
We can't fight it forever.
No! Stay back!
It's okay, you can let go.
Honey, I'm serious.
Don't come any closer.
No.
There's only one way
to end this.
What are you doing?
What I should have done
a long time ago.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Babe,
I used to worry
I wouldn't remember
who I was without you,
but,
the truth is
I remember exactly who I was.
Okay?
I was, I was miserable.
I was incomplete, cold,
so much time wasted
thinking about
some other life
where all my bullshit
adolescent dreams
came true, but,
babe, you are the dream
that came true.
I'm so sorry it
took me so long,
but I just,
I fucking suck and I,
I love you so much.
Close your eyes.
What?
Trust me, close your eyes.
Tim, what are you doing?
This won't end until
one of us is dead.
Okay?
Babe, I don't want you
to see this.
We don't have time, okay?
No, you don't have to.
You don't have to.
It's gonna be okay.
You'll be okay.
Please just drop it.
Just drop it.
Please just-- just drop it.
Babe, babe, babe!
Oh shit!
Oh shit, oh God!
Baby, hey, hey.
Hey, stay with me, baby,
hey yes, yeah, hey,
You gotta run.
You gotta be free.
I'll never be free from you.
Never.
Promise me one thing.
Anything.
You'll make my final post
"BRB dying."
Hey, hey, hey,
Millie, Millie!
No, no, hey, Millie!
Millie! Shit.
Baby, baby.
Baby, stay with me,
please.
No, no, no, baby!
What have you done?
It was the only way
to stop the bleeding.
What?
No.
No, no.
I was trying to let you go.
Did you wanna let me go?
What are you doing?
It's your favorite album,
right?
You remember that?
I always imagined it as
our first dance, but...
because maybe that
won't happen now.
Are you sure you want this?
I do.
I love you.
I love you too.
"When two become one"...
Hey.